

Solaisamy R Senior Accountant

No.14-B, S R Flats Door No.D4

Maduvappar, 1st Street, Lakshmipuram, Shangam Road,

Chromepet, Chennai – 600 044.

Mobile: 9840408905 Email: Solaisamy.r@gmail.com

About Me

I am a Accounts Professional with 15 years of experience and manage to overall general accounting operations by controlling and verifying our all financial transactions, from fixed payments and variable expenses to bank deposits and budgets

Education & Qualification

MBA (Finance)

Bharathiyar University (SDE) 2009

B.Com (Commerce)

SRM College of Arts & Science (UOM)

HSC & SSLC 2004 & S.R. Govt Hr. Sec. School 1999

Tally

CSC Institution 2006

MDCA

SISI Institution 2006

Type Writing

College of Commerce 2004

Personal Details

Father Name :- Raj G

Native :- Sattur, Virudhunagar

DOB & Age :- 12.04.1984 & 39

Marital Status :- Single

Nationality :- Indian

Language :- Tamil, English

Health :- Physically Challenged

Professional Experience

Senior Accountant

Tagore College of Arts and Science
Hilton Mat. Hr. Sec. School
July -2016 to Till Date
May -2013 to October-2014

- Student Fees (Income Booking, Collection and Reconcile)
- Statutory Filing (Epf, Esi, Professional Tax, Income Tax)
- Bank (Receipts, Payment, Contra and Reconcile)
- Payroll
- Annual Budgets
- Coordination to Internal and External Audit

Accountant

Guru Nanak College November 2014 to June 2016

- Student Fees (Income Booking, Collection and Reconcile)
- Statutory Filing (Epf, Esi, Professional Tax, Income Tax)
- Bank (Receipts, Payment, Contra and Reconcile)
- Payroll
- Debtors and Creditors Analysis
- Coordination to Internal and External Audit

Accountant

Aheads e-Solution India Pvt Ltd February 2011 to April 2013

- Debtors & Creditors (Income & Expense Booking, Collection and Reconcile)
- Statutory Filing (Epf, Esi, Professional Tax, Income Tax)
- Bank (Receipts, Payment, Contra and Reconcile)
- Payroll
- Vouching and Book keeping
- Coordination to Internal and External Audit

Accounts Assistant

Mudhra Group of Company March 2010 to January 2011

- Entry to Tally (Invoice and Bills)
- Prepare Sales Register and Update Daily to Director
- Prepare to Bills Discounting or Bill of Exchange
- Attend the Phone (General Enquiry and Payment)

Skills

- Tally Erp
- MS office (Adv. Excel, Word)
- Financial Accounts & Taxation
- Epf, Esi, Professional Tax
- Payroll
- Inventory & Asset Mgmt
- GST (GSTR1, 3B & 2A)
- Income Tax (24Q, 26Q, ITR)
- Strong Analytical Skill